Guide to the Don Patinkin Papers, 1870-1995
Don Patinkin papers 1870-1995
- Correspondence, 1930-1995and undated (Bulk 1950-1995)
  - 1958-1977 (Bulk 1964-1977)and undated
    - Studies in Monetary Econ., 1969, Jan.-1970, July
    - Studies in Monetary Economics, Correspondence,1970, Jul.-1975, May
    - Theil, Prof. Henri, 1968, March-June
    - Tobin,1971,Mar
    - University of the Negev, Dec. 1970-1972,June
    - Wicksells' Cumulative Process in Theory and Practice,1968, April
    - Zussman, Dr., 1968
    - "Chicago filing," 1974-1976, (4 folders)
    - Correspondence - Keynes' Manuscripts,1975
    - Correspondence - Publications, 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 38)
    - Correspondence - University of Chicago, 1976, July-Aug., (2 folders and 2 binders)
    - Course on Agricultural Economics, 1976, June
    - CUNY, 1975-1976
    - Econometric Society, 1974, Feb.-1975, Jan.
    - Econometric Society and Econometrica,1975, Jan.-1977, Jan.
    - Friedman, Milton - Correspondence, 1972-1978
    - General Correspondence - University of Western Ontario, 1976, Sept. 26-Nov. 4
    - Harper and Row, 1974, Nov.-1976, Mar.
    - Hebrew Correspondence, 1976-1977
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975, Aug.-1977, July
    - National Science Foundation Proposal, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
    - Misc. correspondence, Chicago1977
    - On Draft Publication: Published Works, 1974-1975
    - Printed Matters, 1974-1977
    - Western Ontario Keynes' Conference: Correspondence, 1975, May-1976, Feb., (2 folders)
    - Personal Correspondence - Baltimore: late 1955-1956
  - Coded Index, 1957-1977
    - Index, 1957-1975 (Box 39)
      - 1.9.57-29.5.58, Nos. 81-8278
      - 18.12.58-22.12.59, Nos. 4-89
      - 11.1.60-27.11.63, Nos. 90-214
      - 1.1.64-8.12.66, Nos. 215-401
      - 3.1.68-1.1.67, Nos. 402-540
      - 3.1.68-4.10.68, Nos. 541-648
      - 27.9.68-2.4.69, Nos. 649-760
      - 8.4.69-16.3.70, Nos. 761-890 (Box 40)
      - 14.4.70-31.5.73, Nos. A184-A385
      - 6.3.70-22.9.71, Nos. 891-1140
      - 22.9.71-9.6.72, Nos. 1141-1310
      - 22.6.72-11.6.73, Nos. 1311-1460
      - 19.6.73-13.11.75, Nos. 1461-1610
    - Index, 1976-1977
      - A-D, 1976-1977
      - E-G, 1976-1977
      - H, 1976-1977
      - I-L, 1976-1977
      - M-O, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
      - P-Z, 1976-1977
  - 1954-1981 (Bulk 1977-1979)
    - "A" Folder (Box 41)
      - A, Miscellaneous,1978
      - American Economic Review ( AER ), 1975, May-1979, Aug.
      - Academy, 1975, March-1978, Dec.
      - Associacao National de Centros de Pos-Graduacao en Economia (ANPEC), 1977, June-1978, March
      - Arndt, Prof. H. W., The Australian National University, 1978, Oct.-Dec.
      - Artis, Michael, 1978, April-Oct.
      - Aspe, Dr. Pedro, 1979, Aug.
    - "B" Folder
      - Barkai, 1978, Feb.-1979, July
      - Blaug, Prof. Mark, 1978, Aug.-1979, May
      - Brems, Hans, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, 1977, Dec.-1978, March
      - Bridel, Pascal, 1978, Aug.-Sept.
      - Budget - Economics, 1978, Sept.-1979, May
      - B, Miscellaneous,1979
    - Ben-Shackar, 1979
    - Bibliography Style Sheet
    - Book, Anticipations of General Theory
    - Book Contracts, 1954-1979
    - Brenner, Gabrielle - Correspondence, 1977, Jan.-1978, Sept.
    - Brenner, Reuven, 1977, May-1979, Feb.
    - Brenner, Reuven - Doctorate, 1977, Oct.-1979, June
    - Broadcasting Authority, 1978, June-Oct.
    - Business 303, 1979, Feb.-June
    - "C" Folder
      - C, Miscellaneous,1978
      - Cameron, R. - Journal of Econ. History,1977, Sept.-1979, July
      - Chabra, S. S., Freeman Book Company, 1978, Aug.-Sept.
      - Chicago Tradition, 1979, Feb.-Aug.
      - Coats, A. W., 1977, May-1979, Aug.
      - Chernow, Barbara H., The Free Press, 1977, Aug.-1978, Oct.
    - Cowles Commission, 1979, Feb.-May
    - Clower, Robert, 1977, Oct.-1979, Aug.
    - Course: Econ. 330 Final Exams,1977,Autumn
    - Currie, L., 1979, June-July
    - "D" Folder
      - Davis, E. G., 1978, Aug.
      - Davis, J. R., University of Fla., 1977, Oct.-1978, March
      - Duke University Press, 1977, June-1979, June
      - Duke University Press - Williams, Ms. B., 1977, Oct.-1978, Oct.
      - D, Miscellaneous,1979
    - Dunlop, John T.,; Harvard University, 1978, Aug.
    - Dvoretsky, 1978, Feb.-March
    - "E" Folder
      - The Economic Journal, 1977, Sept.-1978, March
      - Eisenstadt, Maggie, Falk Institute, 1977, Sept.-1979, July
      - E, Miscellaneous, 1979, April-1980, Jan.
    - "F" Folder
      - F, Miscellaneous, 1977, Nov.-1979, July
      - Falk Institute, 1978, Feb.-1979, April
      - Farmiloe, T. M., 1977, March -1979, Aug.
      - Final Report of IFT on Research Project Entitled The Dev. of Keynes' Monetary Thought,1978, Jan.
      - Fischer, Prof. Stanley, MIT, 1977, July-1979, Aug.
      - Flemming, Prof. J.S., The Economic Journal, Nuffield College, 1978, June-Nov.
      - The Free Press (Division of Macmillan) 1977, Sept.
    - "G" Folder (Box 42)
      - G, Miscellaneous, 1979, Jan.-March
      - Goodhart, C. A. E. - Bank of England, 1977, Sept.-Dec.
      - Goodwin, C. D. - Duke University, 1977, Aug.-1979, Aug.
      - Gordon, Robert, 1978, May-June
    - "H" Folder
      - Harberger, Al, 1977, Sept-1978, Aug.
      - Harcourt, G. C., University of Adelaide, 1979, Jan.-Feb.
      - Hebrew Encyclopedia, 1977, Sept.-Nov.
      - Hebrew University - Advanced Studies,1978, Feb,-1979, May
      - Howitt, P., University of Western Ontario, 1977, Aug.-1979, Aug.
      - H, Miscellaneous, 1978, Jan.-Sept.
    - Hebrew University, Dept. of Economics,1979
    - Hebrew University, Seltzer, 1978, April-Sept.
    - Hoxter, Curtis J., 1978, May-Sept.
    - "I" Folder
      - Institute for International Economic Studies - Sweden, 1977, Nov.-1979, April
      - International Economic Association, 1977, June-Dec.
      - Israel Foundation Trustees, 1978, Feb.-1979, Aug.
      - I, Miscellaneous, 1978, Dec.-1979, April
    - Insurance Policies, 1978, Dec.
    - "J" Folder
      - J, Miscellaneous, 1977-1979
    - Johnson, Elizabeth
    - Johnson, Harry, 1977, Dec.-1978, Feb.
    - Journal of Macroeconomics, 1977, Aug.-1978, May
    - "K" Folder
      - K, Miscellaneous, 1979, July-Aug.
      - Keynes' Monetary Thought, Revisions, 1978, Dec.
      - Keynes' Monetary Thought, 1979, Feb.
      - Kleiman, 1978, Feb.-1979, March
      - Kop, Y., Maurice Falk Institute, 1977, Oct.-1979, May
    - "L" Folder
      - L, Miscellaneous, 1977, Oct.-Dec
      - Laidler, D., University of Western Ontario, 1977, Nov.-1979, May
      - Leith, J. C., University of Western Ontario, 1977, Oct.-1979, Aug.
      - Lerner, Prof. Abba, 1978, Oct.
      - Levinson, Jacob, Bank Hapoalim B. M., 1978, Aug.-Dec.
    - "M" Folder
      - M, Miscellaneous
      - Maital, Shlomo, 1977, Nov.-1979, July
      - Marschak, Jacob, 1977, Dec.-1978, Feb.
      - Mayer, Thomas, 1977, Dec.-1978, Nov.
      - Mehta, Prof. Granshyam, University of Queensland, 1978, Aug.-Sept.
      - Miller, Prof. James Slavic Review, 1978, Feb.-May
      - Moggridge, D. University of Toronto, 1978, July-1979, Aug.
      - Mints, L.W. July -1979, Aug.
      - Money, Interest, and Prices - Patinkin, 1977, Oct.
      - Mosby, Carolyn, University of Chicago - Economics, 1979, Oct.
    - Musu, Prof. Ignazio, Universita` Degli Studi di Venezia, 1977, Dec.-1978, Oct. (Box 42)
    - "N" Folder
      - Nef, John U., 1979, July
      - N, Miscellaneous, 1978, Jan.-1979, Feb.
    - "NSF" Folder
      - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1979, Feb.
      - NSF, 1978, Dec.Proposal
      - NSF, Current, 1979, July
      - NSF, Application Procedures, 1978, Nov.
      - NSF Patinkin, Appropriations Ledger, 1979, June-1980, Dec.
      - NSF, 1978, MarchProposal
      - NSF, 1977-78 Grant
      - NSF, Documents
      - NSF, Reporting Procedures, 1979, Feb.
    - "O" Folder (Box 43)
      - Opie, Redvers, 1977, July-Nov.
      - O, Miscellaneous, 1979, March-June
    - "P" Folder
      - P, Miscellaneous, 1977, Nov.-1978, Nov.
      - Perlman, Mark, 1977, Aug.-1978, Nov.
      - Permissions - Chicago School, 1979, March-1981, June
      - Presley, Dr. John, University of Loughborough, 1977, Aug.-1978, Dec.
    - "Patinkin Personal" Folder
      - Patinkin's Change of Address Itinerary, 1979, Sept.-Oct.
      - Patinkin Personal - Insurance, 1977, Jan.-1979, Aug.
      - Patinkin Personal - Bank Leumi, 1977, Oct.-1979, Aug.
      - Patinkin Personal - Publications, 1978, April-Nov.
      - Patinkin Personal - Pension, 1978, Nov.-1979, Aug.
      - Personal Correspondence, 1978, Oct.-1979, March
    - "Q" Folder
      - Quarterly Journal of Economics, 1978, May
    - "R" Folder
      - R, miscellaneous,1977-78
      - Reviews, KMT,1977- 1981
      - Reviews - Keynes and Cambridge, 1978, May-1979, Feb.
      - Robinson, Prof. Sir Austin, The Marshall Library, Feb.- 1978, Oct.
    - Reading Lists,1978
    - A Re-examination of Keynesian Economics: Research Proposal, 1976, March-July (Box 43)
    - Royal Economic Society, 1973, April-1979, Aug.
    - "Roberts" Folder
      - Roberts, David, 1977, Feb.-1978, May
      - Roberts, David L., 1955, Sept.-1972, Feb.
      - Roberts, David L. 1977, Aug.-Oct.
    - Royalties, 1979, June-1980, Aug.
    - Rymes, Prof. T. K., Carleton University, 1978, Dec.
    - "S" Folder
      - S, Miscellaneous, 1979, April-July
      - The Pinhas Sapir Center For Development, Tel Aviv University, 1979, April-July
      - Simon, Herbert A., 1978, Oct.-1979, Aug.
      - Stigler, Prof. George, Journal of Political Economy, 1977, Oct.-1978, Sept.
      - Stone, Prof. George, University of Cambridge, 1977, Aug.-1978, Nov.
      - Strategic and International Studies, Center of, 1978, May-1979, Feb.
    - Spiro, Peter, 1977, Nov.-1978, Jan.
    - "T" Folder
      - T, Miscellaneous, 1978, May-1979, June
      - Thweatt, Prof. William O., Vanderbilt University, 1978, March-August
      - TIAA, 1978, March-1979, July
      - Trescott, Prof. Paul B., Southern Illinois University, 1978, Sept.
    - "U" Folder
      - U, Miscellaneous, 1978, May-1979, May
      - University of Toronto Press, 1978, Jan.-1979, Aug.
      - University of Chicago Press, 1978, Dec.-1977, Oct.
    - "V" Folder
      - V, Miscellaneous, 1979, March-June
      - Vargas Foundation, 1979, March
    - "W" Folder
      - W, Miscellaneous,1978
      - Weintraub, Prof. Roy, 1977-1978
      - Wells, Prof. Paul, 1978, June-1979, Jan.
    - X-Y-Z, Miscellaneous, 1978, Oct.-1979, Aug.
  - Correspondence, 1924-1987, (Bulk 1980-1982)and undated
    - Academic Press, 1980, Mar. (Box 43)
    - Acadron (H.U. Printing and Publishing House), 1980, May-1981, Jan.
    - Aereni, 1979, Nov.-Dec.
    - Aizenmen, Yehoshua, 1979, July-Dec.
    - American Economic Review - 1979, Feb.
    - American Express, 1979, Dec.-1982, Feb.
    - American Scholar, 1980, Jan.-Feb.
    - Anticipations of General Theory - Comments, 1980, May
    - Anticipations of General Theory - Permissions, 1979, Sept.-Oct.
    - Argentina, 1987, Aug.
    - Assistance Fund, 1979, Nov.-1980, Feb.
    - Aspe, Pedro, 1979, Oct.-1982, July
    - Avneri, Shlomo, 1980-1982
    - Beale Travel Service, 1979, Oct.-Dec. (Box 44)
    - Becker, Gary, 1980, Jan.
    - Belka, Marek, 1979, Oct.-1980, Sept.
    - Ben-Porat,Yoram, 1979, Nov.
    - Blaug, Mark, University of London, 1979, Oct.
    - Books Ordered, 1982, Jan.-Aug.
    - Borg, Finn, 1979, Dec.-1980, Aug.
    - Borts, Editor, 1980, Jan.-July
    - Brody, Norman, 1979, Sept.-1980, Oct.
    - Bronfenbrenner, Martin, 1980, Jan.-1982, Jan.
    - California, 1979, Aug.-1980, May
    - Cameron, Rondo/Co., 1979, Oct.-1980, Feb.
    - Center for Advanced Study, California, undated
    - Ceriani, Luigi, 1979, Dec.-1982, Feb.
    - Cherow, Barbara, 1980, Jan.-June
    - Chisholm, Derek, 1979, Nov.-Dec.
    - Chiswick, C. U., 1979, Aug.-1980, Feb.
    - Clower, Robert, 1980, Jan.-1982, Feb.
    - Clark, Colin: University of Queensland, 1932, Oct.-1981, Sept.
    - Collis, J.: University of Western Ontario, 1978, Mar.- 1979, Oct.
    - Columbia University, 1980, Sept.-1982, June
    - Columbia University, 1982, Jan.
    - Conferences - Finland, 1980, June
    - Correspondence, 1978, Jan.-Sept.
    - Council of the Faculty of Social Sciences, 1979, Dec.-1980, Feb. (Box 44)
    - Crawford, 1980, Jan.-Apr.
    - Currie, Lauchlin, 1972, Oct.-1990
    - Daehler-Wilking, Richard, 1979, Dec.-1980, Aug.
    - De Marchi, Neil, 1979, Nov.-1982, May
    - Diagrams, undated
    - Ditting, 1980, July-1981, Sept.
    - Drazen, Allan, 1980, Apr.-Nov.
    - Dreze, J. H., 1980, May-1982, Apr.
    - Duke University Press
      - 1979, Sept.-1982, Apr., (2 folders)
      - Poole, Anne, 1979, Aug.-1981, Feb.
      - Saros, T. A., 1977, Oct.-1981
    - Economics and Personal, 1980, Mar.-May
    - Economics Department, 1979, Nov.
    - Economics Department, 1980, Mar.-1981, July
    - Efroymson, Clarence, 1979, Oct.-1982, May
    - Elkana, Yehuda, 1967, June-1982, Apr.
    - European University Institute, 1981, Mar.-1982, May
    - Falk Budget, 1980, Aug.-1982, May
    - Falk Institute: Budget, 1980, Jan.-Apr.
    - Falk Institute, Member, 1980, Mar.
    - Fall,1979, (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - Feiwel, G., 1980, Feb.
    - Financial, 1980, Jan.-Apr.
    - Fischer, Stanley, 1980, Apr.-1982, June
    - Fitoussi, Jean-Paul, 1980, May-1982, June
    - Ford Foundation, 1980-1982
    - Ford Foundation:
      - 1980, May-1982, Apr.
      - Receipts, 1982, Apr.
    - Frankel, 1979, Nov.-Dec.
    - Friedland, C., 1979, June-1980, Aug.
    - von Furstenberg, G. M., 1980, Feb.-May
    - Gaaton, Dr. A. L., 1979, Oct.
    - General Correspondence: A-Z, 1979-1981, (4 folders)
    - Goodwin, Craufurd, 1979, Sept.-1982, Jan.
    - GSB:
      - 1979, Mar.-July
      - Richard Daehler Wilking, 1979, Aug.-Oct.
    - Hahn, Frank, 1980, Apr.-Aug.
    - Hansen, Bent, 1978, Feb.-1980, Sept.
    - Harper and Row, N.Y., 1977-1982,June
    - Hickman, B. G., 1979, Nov.-Dec.
    - Hoisington, T., 1970, Dec.-1979, Mar.
    - Hollander, Samuel, 1980, Mar.-Dec.
    - Horovitz, 1980, July
    - Howitt, Peter, 1979, Nov.-1982, May
    - Hebrew University Professors' Organization, 1980, Feb.
    - Income Tax, 1979-1981, (3 folders) (Box 46)
    - Israel Economic Association, 1980, Apr.
    - Israel Foundation Trustees, 1980-1982, (2 folders)
    - Jaffe, William, 1951, July-1979, Aug.
    - Jerusalem: Mailing, undated
    - Jonung, Lars, 1924-1980,July
    - Journal of Money, Credit and Banking, 1980, Aug.-1982, June
    - Journals: Subscriptions, 1979, Dec.-1982, June
    - Hirotaka, Kato, 1977, Aug.-1980, Nov.
    - Keynes, Milo, 1980, Mar.-July
    - Killam Program: Ottawa, 1979, Sept.-Oct.
    - Kleiman, Ephraim, 1979, Dec.-1987, Sept.
    - Klein, Lawrence, 1980, Jan.-Dec., 1981
    - Kuznets, Simon, 1979, Dec.-1982, May
    - Laidler, Davis, 1980, Mar.-1982, May
    - Lancaster, Kelvin, 1979, Dec.-1982, June
    - Lange, Felicia, 1980, Aug.-Oct.
    - Aski, K. L., 1980, Apr.-1981, Feb.
    - Leith, Clark J., 1979, Sept.-1982, June
    - Lerner, Abba, 1979, Nov.-1981, Sept.
    - Levin, Marc, 1979, Nov.-1981, July
    - Lewin, Paulina, 1979, Mar.-May
    - Lindbeck, Assar, 1980, May-July
    - Lowe, Barbara, 1979, Aug.-1982, Feb.
    - Lucas, Robert E.: Editor, Journal of Political Economy,1979, Oct.-1980, Nov.
    - Maital, Shlomo, 1980, Apr.-1981, Apr.
    - Mailing lists, 1980, July-1981, Sept.
    - Manuscript, 1979-1980,Jan.
    - Maps (Robert Douwna, Prints and Maps), 1979, July-1980, May
    - Marshall, Field, 1980, May-June
    - Marty, A. L., 1979, Sept.-Oct.
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co, 1981, Feb.-June
    - Mediterranean: Dead Sea Canal, 1980, Aug.-1987, June
    - Merton, Robert, 1968-1982,June
    - Moggridge, Donald, 1980-1981,Jan. (Box 47)
    - Millman, S., 1980, June-1982, Apr.
    - Muller-Wille, Christopher, 1979, Nov.-1980, Aug.
    - Mundell, 1980
    - Mundell, Robert, 1980, Nov.-1982, June
    - Mundlak, Yair, 1980, June.
    - National Pen Corporation, 1979-1980,Jan.
    - Ne'enam, Yuval, 1987, Mar.-May
    - The New Yorker, 1981, Mar.-June
    - New York University, 1979, Oct.-1982, June
    - NSF - Grant Information, 1979, Jan.
    - NSF, 1980-1982,Feb.
    - Ohlin, Bertil, 1977, Sept.-1979, July
    - Opie, Redvers, 1979, Oct.
    - Osiatynski, Jerzy, 1980, May-1981, Sept.
    - Overmann, Ronald, 1979, Oct.-Nov.
    - Pagett, Richard, 1980, Apr.-May
    - Paunio, Jouko, 1979, Nov.-1980, June
    - Pensions, 1979, Nov.
    - Personal, 1980, June-Nov.
    - Photographs, undated
    - Professors' Organization,1980, Feb-1981, Nov.
    - Quarterly Journal of Economics, 1942, July-1979, Dec.
    - Rapping, Leonard, 1979, Mar.-Dec.
    - Recommendations, 1979, Nov.-1981, Nov.
    - Rector, 1982, Mar.-May
    - Referee Reports, 1979, Feb.-1981, Mar.
    - Reimbursements, 1980, Apr.-Oct.
    - Research and Development Grants, 1980, Jan.-Mar.
    - Research Students Committee, 1980, July-Aug.
    - Rising Grants Committee, 1979, Mar.-June
    - Robinson, Austin, 1937-1981,Aug.
    - Robinson, Joan, 1978, Aug.-1981, Feb.
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1978, Nov.-1981, Mar.
    - Rolph, Earl R., 1980, Mar.-May
    - Rosett, Richard N., 1977, Nov.-1981, Oct.
    - Royalties, 1980, June-1981, Oct.
    - Rubenstein, Ariel, 1980, Jan.-Apr.
    - Salant, Walter S., 1979, Oct.
    - Samuelson, Paul, 1972, Apr.-1982, May
    - Seiler, Ellen, 1979, Oct.-1981, Jan.
    - Senate, 1979, Nov.-1980, Feb.
    - Sidrauski, Miguel, 1980, Nov.
    - Smyth, David J., 1980, Mar.-1982, May.
    - Steiger, Otto, 1979, Feb.-1982, Jan.
    - Stigler,George, 1979, Dec.-1980, Aug. (Box 48)
    - Study Fund, 1980, Aug.-Nov.
    - Swoboda, Alexander K., 1979, Oct.-1980, Feb.
    - Taylor, Lewis, 1976, Oct.-1980, Jan.
    - Technion: Israel Institute of Technology, 1979, Jan.-1980, Mar.
    - TIAA (Teachers Insurance and Annuity of America), 1980, Jan.-Oct., (2 folders)
    - Tobin, James, 1980, Jan.-1982, Apr.
    - Topp, Niels-Henrik, 1980, Jan.-Mar.
    - Toronto University, 1979, May
    - U.S. Department of Justice, 1979, Aug.
    - U.S. Income Tax, 1975, Nov.-1978, Dec.
    - University of Chicago:
      - Department of Economics, 1980, Mar.-1982, Feb.
      - Journal of Political Economy, 1980, May-June
      - Library, 1980, Feb.-May
    - University of Chicago: Department, 1972, Aug.-1980 Aug.
    - University of Chicago Press:
      - Alice Bennett, 1979, Feb.-1982, June
      - Robert Berg, 1981, Sept.-Dec.
    - University of Chicago Press: Liz Johnson, 1978, June-1982, July
    - University of Chicago Staff List, Economics,1979,Spr.
    - University of Western Ontario, Cudmore, 1979-1980
    - University of Western Ontario, Economics Dept.: Melvin, J., 1978, Feb.-1979, Aug.
    - Weiserbs, Daniel, 1980
    - Wellisz, Stainislaw, 1979-1982
    - Western Hemisphere, Inc.,1979
    - Western Ontario, 1979-1980
    - Who's Who, 1979, May-1982, May
    - Yellin, Larry, 1979-1981
    - Zelinsky, Daniel, 1979-1980
    - Zeltser, D., 1980, June-July
    - Zeyria, Yossi, nd
    - Zisook, Jerrold, 1979-1982
  - Correspondence, 1977-1987 (Bulk 1982-1986)and undated
    - A, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 48)
    - Abramowitz, Moses, 1980, Dec.-1982, Jan.
    - American Economic Association, Jan.1983-June 1985
    - American Journal of Sociology, Aug.1982-Jan. 1985
    - Anticipations, 1981-1986
    - Autobiography,1982
    - Asimakopulos, May 1981-May 1986
    - B, Miscellaneous, 1982-1986
    - Banca D'Italia, 1983-1984
    - Barens, 1983
    - Blaug, 1983-1986
    - Book Contracts, 1979-1980
    - Book Orders, 1982-1986
    - Budget Funds, 1984-1986, (3 folders) (Box 49)
    - C, Miscellaneous, 1982-1985
    - Cambridge University Press,1982
    - Chandler, 1985
    - Cipolla, Carlo, 1983-1985
    - Cohen, Louis (University of Chicago, Medical), 1982-1984
    - Correspondence, Feb.1981-Dec. 1983
    - Correspondence, 1982-1983
    - Correspondence, 1986, Aug.-1986, Dec.
    - Correspondence, 1986, Dec.-1987, Feb.
    - D, Miscellaneous,1985
    - Davidson, Sidney, 1982-1985
    - E, Miscellaneous, 1985-1986
    - Efroymson, 1984-1986
    - European University Institute, 1982-1985
    - F, Miscellaneous, 1983-1986
    - Fitoussi, 1982-1986
    - Florida University, 1982-1988
    - Ford Foundation,1982
    - Frenkel, 1983-1985
    - Friedland, 1982-1985
    - Friedman, Milton, 1978-1985
    - G, Miscellaneous, 1980-1986
    - Goodwin, 1982-85
    - Goodwin, 1986
    - Gorden, 1983-1986
    - Griliches, Zvi, 1982-1985
    - H, Miscellaneous, 1982-1986 (Box 50)
    - Hahn, 1982-1986
    - Harper and Row, 1980-1986
    - Heffers, 1983-1986
    - Hirshleifer, 1983-1985
    - Hollander, Sam, 1984-1986
    - Hoover Institute, 1985
    - Howitt, Peter, 1982, Dec.-1986, July
    - I, Miscellaneous, 1984-1986
    - I. E. A., 1982-1986
    - Income Tax, 1983-1986
    - Insurance, 1982-1986
    - Invitations for Articles and Lectures, 1982-1986
    - Israel Foundation Trustees, 1982-1985
    - Itineraries, 1983-1985
    - J, Miscellaneous, 1985-1986
    - K, Miscellaneous, 1983-1986
    - Kaleck, 1984-1986
    - Keynes' Centenary, 1982-1983
    - Kleiman, 1985-1986
    - Kuznets, 1982-1986
    - L, Miscellaneous, 1982-1986
    - Laidler, 1983-1986
    - M, Miscellaneous, 1983-1986
    - McCallum, 1986
    - Merton, 1982-1984
    - Multiple Discoveries, 1984-1985
    - New York University,1983-1985
    - O, Miscellaneous, 1979-1986
    - Osiatynski, 1983-1986
    - P, Miscellaneous, 1982-1985
    - Palgrave Dictionary of Economics, 1984-1986
    - Parkin, 1984-1985 (Box 51)
    - Patinkin - Personal and Photos, 1983-1986
    - Permissions, 1983-1986
    - Patinkin, Personal1981-1984, (3 folders)
    - Pittsburgh University, 1985-1986
    - Princeton, 1983-1985
    - Protose, 1979-1985
    - Purchases, 1982-1986
    - R, Miscellaneous, 1977-1986
    - Recommendations, 1982-1986
    - Referee's Reports - Correspondence, 1982-1986
    - Review Articles/Requests, 1983-1986
    - Rosovsky, 1982-1985
    - Rothberg, 1982-1986
    - Royal Economic Society (journal), 1982-1985
    - Royalties, 1982-1985
    - Rymes, 1982-1985
    - S, Miscellaneous, 1982-1986
    - Samuelson, 1982-1984
    - Sebastiani, 1986
    - Solow, 1981-1982
    - Stigler, 1982-1986
    - Subscriptions, 1982-1986
    - T, Miscellaneous, 1982-1986
    - U, Miscellaneous,1985
    - University of Western Ontario,1983
    - V and W, Miscellaneous, 1985-1986
    - Walker, 1985-1986
    - Weintraub, E. Roy, 1983-1986 (Box 52)
    - Who's Who, 1982-1986
    - Zelinsky, 1983-1986
    - Zisook, 1983-1984
  - Correspondence, 1941-1995 (Bulk 1987-1995)and undated
    - Aran Patinkin, 1970, May-1994 (Box 52)
    - Asimakopulos, Athanasios, 1988, May-1992, Nov.
    - Atkinson, Tony, 1989, Oct.-1992, Sept.
    - Accident, 1991, Feb.-Aug.
    - Academy (The Israel Academy of Sciences and Humanities), 1988, May-1995, Aug.
    - Allen, William, 1990, Oct.-1995, Feb.
    - American Economist, 1986, Mar.
    - Baker, 1988-1989
    - Banca D'Italia, 1987, Apr.-1993, Nov.
    - Barens, Ingo, 1983-1995
    - Barro, Robert, 1992, Dec.-1993, Sept.
    - Bateman, Bradley W., 1989, Feb.-1995, Jan.
    - Benassy, Jean-Pascal, 1986, June-1987, June
    - Bensusan-Butt, David, 1991, Sept.-1994, July
    - Blaug, Mark, 1987, Apr.-1991, Nov.
    - Blaug, M. and Shaw, G. K., 1989, May-1991, Dec.
    - Bodkin, Ronald G., 1941, June-1989, Jan.
    - Bogomolov, Oleg, 1989-1993
    - Boianovsky, Mauro, 1990-1994
    - Books Ordered, 1986-1992
    - Brady, Michael E., 1988, May (Box 53)
    - British Academy, 1968, Nov.-1993, June
    - Brody, Norman, 1990, Mar.-Sept.
    - Buchanan, James, 1988-1993
    - Cati, Matteo, 1988, Sept.-1990, May
    - Chick, Victoria, 1990, May-1995, May
    - Chapple, Simon, 1988, Oct.-1994, Feb.
    - Clark, Colin, 1988, Aug.-1990, Apr.
    - Clower, Robert, 1987, Mar.-1994, Apr.
    - Goddington, Alan, 1979, Dec.-1980, Jan.